[
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"試験\"?",
    "word": "試験",
    "options": [
      "ひどい",
      "しけん",
      "とまる",
      "うつくしい"
    ],
    "correct": "しけん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"辞書\"?",
    "word": "辞書",
    "options": [
      "じしょ",
      "わすれる",
      "つたえる",
      "かなしむ"
    ],
    "correct": "じしょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"宿題\"?",
    "word": "宿題",
    "options": [
      "ならう",
      "かわく",
      "るすばん",
      "しゅくだい"
    ],
    "correct": "しゅくだい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"意味\"?",
    "word": "意味",
    "options": [
      "ぶんか",
      "ほうほう",
      "はこぶ",
      "いみ"
    ],
    "correct": "いみ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"最近\"?",
    "word": "最近",
    "options": [
      "じかん",
      "まち",
      "にる",
      "さいきん"
    ],
    "correct": "さいきん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"場所\"?",
    "word": "場所",
    "options": [
      "ばしょ",
      "ぎょうじ",
      "せんたくする",
      "しょうたいする"
    ],
    "correct": "ばしょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"工場\"?",
    "word": "工場",
    "options": [
      "せいじ",
      "かんばん",
      "かたい",
      "こうじょう"
    ],
    "correct": "こうじょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"案内する\"?",
    "word": "案内する",
    "options": [
      "ほんやく",
      "しゅうまつ",
      "こども",
      "あんないする"
    ],
    "correct": "あんないする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"準備する\"?",
    "word": "準備する",
    "options": [
      "おる",
      "じゅんびする",
      "こしょう",
      "かなしむ"
    ],
    "correct": "じゅんびする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"連絡する\"?",
    "word": "連絡する",
    "options": [
      "うんどう",
      "れんらくする",
      "さびしい",
      "かいわ"
    ],
    "correct": "れんらくする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"相談する\"?",
    "word": "相談する",
    "options": [
      "きじ",
      "そうだんする",
      "けっせき",
      "べんり"
    ],
    "correct": "そうだんする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"注意する\"?",
    "word": "注意する",
    "options": [
      "ちゅういする",
      "あんない",
      "まにあう",
      "むかう"
    ],
    "correct": "ちゅういする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"反対する\"?",
    "word": "反対する",
    "options": [
      "あげる",
      "しま",
      "みなと",
      "はんたいする"
    ],
    "correct": "はんたいする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"賛成する\"?",
    "word": "賛成する",
    "options": [
      "けっせき",
      "さんせいする",
      "しぜん",
      "かよう"
    ],
    "correct": "さんせいする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"説明する\"?",
    "word": "説明する",
    "options": [
      "ものがたり",
      "かく",
      "こしょう",
      "せつめいする"
    ],
    "correct": "せつめいする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"参加する\"?",
    "word": "参加する",
    "options": [
      "かえる",
      "かじ",
      "さんかする",
      "ちょうし"
    ],
    "correct": "さんかする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"招待する\"?",
    "word": "招待する",
    "options": [
      "やせる",
      "しょうたいする",
      "きかい",
      "しんぶん"
    ],
    "correct": "しょうたいする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"心配する\"?",
    "word": "心配する",
    "options": [
      "じこ",
      "でんわ",
      "しんぱいする",
      "ふる"
    ],
    "correct": "しんぱいする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"安心する\"?",
    "word": "安心する",
    "options": [
      "こくさい",
      "こわい",
      "さいきん",
      "あんしんする"
    ],
    "correct": "あんしんする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"計算する\"?",
    "word": "計算する",
    "options": [
      "ふゆ",
      "わかす",
      "いためる",
      "けいさんする"
    ],
    "correct": "けいさんする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"予約する\"?",
    "word": "予約する",
    "options": [
      "よやくする",
      "りょうりする",
      "うたう",
      "わすれる"
    ],
    "correct": "よやくする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"約束する\"?",
    "word": "約束する",
    "options": [
      "やくそくする",
      "たいよう",
      "やせる",
      "しゅんかん"
    ],
    "correct": "やくそくする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"復習する\"?",
    "word": "復習する",
    "options": [
      "みなと",
      "さいきん",
      "ふくしゅうする",
      "かんじる"
    ],
    "correct": "ふくしゅうする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"予習する\"?",
    "word": "予習する",
    "options": [
      "せつめいする",
      "ふゆ",
      "じゆう",
      "よしゅうする"
    ],
    "correct": "よしゅうする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"練習する\"?",
    "word": "練習する",
    "options": [
      "げつまつ",
      "おしえる",
      "かつどう",
      "れんしゅうする"
    ],
    "correct": "れんしゅうする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"運転する\"?",
    "word": "運転する",
    "options": [
      "にる",
      "うんてんする",
      "けしき",
      "ふえる"
    ],
    "correct": "うんてんする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"散歩する\"?",
    "word": "散歩する",
    "options": [
      "かじ",
      "くるしむ",
      "だんせい",
      "さんぽする"
    ],
    "correct": "さんぽする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"洗濯する\"?",
    "word": "洗濯する",
    "options": [
      "あんしんする",
      "ちょうし",
      "ちり",
      "せんたくする"
    ],
    "correct": "せんたくする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"掃除する\"?",
    "word": "掃除する",
    "options": [
      "さいきん",
      "みつかる",
      "そうじする",
      "きかん"
    ],
    "correct": "そうじする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"料理する\"?",
    "word": "料理する",
    "options": [
      "ばしょ",
      "じだい",
      "しごと",
      "りょうりする"
    ],
    "correct": "りょうりする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"食事する\"?",
    "word": "食事する",
    "options": [
      "しょうせつ",
      "しょくじする",
      "きびしい",
      "しゅみ"
    ],
    "correct": "しょくじする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"見学する\"?",
    "word": "見学する",
    "options": [
      "けんがくする",
      "ぶんがく",
      "ざっし",
      "ならう"
    ],
    "correct": "けんがくする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"見物する\"?",
    "word": "見物する",
    "options": [
      "けんぶつする",
      "とまる",
      "こうじょう",
      "けしき"
    ],
    "correct": "けんぶつする"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"関係\"?",
    "word": "関係",
    "options": [
      "おどろく",
      "ぬれる",
      "かんけい",
      "とまる"
    ],
    "correct": "かんけい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"世界\"?",
    "word": "世界",
    "options": [
      "すばらしい",
      "せかい",
      "みつける",
      "へんじ"
    ],
    "correct": "せかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"自分\"?",
    "word": "自分",
    "options": [
      "じぶん",
      "まち",
      "こくさい",
      "とまる"
    ],
    "correct": "じぶん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"自由\"?",
    "word": "自由",
    "options": [
      "とまる",
      "じゆう",
      "しま",
      "なつ"
    ],
    "correct": "じゆう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"理由\"?",
    "word": "理由",
    "options": [
      "かつどう",
      "ばしょ",
      "かじ",
      "りゆう"
    ],
    "correct": "りゆう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"社会\"?",
    "word": "社会",
    "options": [
      "かわく",
      "にんげん",
      "つなみ",
      "しゃかい"
    ],
    "correct": "しゃかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"文化\"?",
    "word": "文化",
    "options": [
      "まんが",
      "さんかする",
      "しょうせつ",
      "ぶんか"
    ],
    "correct": "ぶんか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"歴史\"?",
    "word": "歴史",
    "options": [
      "れきし",
      "じゆう",
      "こうじょう",
      "しゃかい"
    ],
    "correct": "れきし"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"地理\"?",
    "word": "地理",
    "options": [
      "ちり",
      "はずかしい",
      "しらべる",
      "とどける"
    ],
    "correct": "ちり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"科学\"?",
    "word": "科学",
    "options": [
      "くらべる",
      "いわう",
      "ほんやく",
      "かがく"
    ],
    "correct": "かがく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"文学\"?",
    "word": "文学",
    "options": [
      "かなしむ",
      "じょうず",
      "へた",
      "ぶんがく"
    ],
    "correct": "ぶんがく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"数学\"?",
    "word": "数学",
    "options": [
      "かるい",
      "さいご",
      "しょるい",
      "すうがく"
    ],
    "correct": "すうがく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"法律\"?",
    "word": "法律",
    "options": [
      "うんてんする",
      "ほうりつ",
      "しらべる",
      "べんり"
    ],
    "correct": "ほうりつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"経済\"?",
    "word": "経済",
    "options": [
      "けいざい",
      "あんない",
      "へんじ",
      "きかい"
    ],
    "correct": "けいざい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"政治\"?",
    "word": "政治",
    "options": [
      "つうやく",
      "しょくぶつ",
      "せいじ",
      "あげる"
    ],
    "correct": "せいじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"国際\"?",
    "word": "国際",
    "options": [
      "じだい",
      "こくさい",
      "かなしむ",
      "せんたくする"
    ],
    "correct": "こくさい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"試合\"?",
    "word": "試合",
    "options": [
      "ふべん",
      "あう",
      "とくい",
      "しあい"
    ],
    "correct": "しあい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"運動\"?",
    "word": "運動",
    "options": [
      "くらべる",
      "まにあう",
      "こわす",
      "うんどう"
    ],
    "correct": "うんどう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"活動\"?",
    "word": "活動",
    "options": [
      "やくそくする",
      "ぎじゅつ",
      "きかん",
      "かつどう"
    ],
    "correct": "かつどう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"生活\"?",
    "word": "生活",
    "options": [
      "せいかつ",
      "くらべる",
      "けんがくする",
      "わかす"
    ],
    "correct": "せいかつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"習慣\"?",
    "word": "習慣",
    "options": [
      "ふべん",
      "しゅうかん",
      "ねむる",
      "きめる"
    ],
    "correct": "しゅうかん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"機会\"?",
    "word": "機会",
    "options": [
      "へんじ",
      "けしき",
      "しぜん",
      "きかい"
    ],
    "correct": "きかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"技術\"?",
    "word": "技術",
    "options": [
      "くるしむ",
      "ただしい",
      "ぎじゅつ",
      "へんじ"
    ],
    "correct": "ぎじゅつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"方法\"?",
    "word": "方法",
    "options": [
      "ちょうし",
      "しゅうかん",
      "ふとる",
      "ほうほう"
    ],
    "correct": "ほうほう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"道具\"?",
    "word": "道具",
    "options": [
      "こうじょう",
      "やわらかい",
      "きじ",
      "どうぐ"
    ],
    "correct": "どうぐ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"家具\"?",
    "word": "家具",
    "options": [
      "かぐ",
      "だんせい",
      "ねんまつ",
      "かじ"
    ],
    "correct": "かぐ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"具合\"?",
    "word": "具合",
    "options": [
      "ふく",
      "ぐあい",
      "けんがくする",
      "べんり"
    ],
    "correct": "ぐあい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"調子\"?",
    "word": "調子",
    "options": [
      "ちょうし",
      "つき",
      "きけん",
      "ひつよう"
    ],
    "correct": "ちょうし"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"気分\"?",
    "word": "気分",
    "options": [
      "おこる",
      "きぶん",
      "すてる",
      "めずらしい"
    ],
    "correct": "きぶん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"気持ち\"?",
    "word": "気持ち",
    "options": [
      "せんたくする",
      "じしょ",
      "きもち",
      "べんり"
    ],
    "correct": "きもち"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"興味\"?",
    "word": "興味",
    "options": [
      "げつまつ",
      "ならぶ",
      "じぶん",
      "きょうみ"
    ],
    "correct": "きょうみ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"趣味\"?",
    "word": "趣味",
    "options": [
      "しゅみ",
      "しま",
      "わる",
      "ほうりつ"
    ],
    "correct": "しゅみ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"特急\"?",
    "word": "特急",
    "options": [
      "とっきゅう",
      "ばんぐみ",
      "しけん",
      "のぞむ"
    ],
    "correct": "とっきゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"急行\"?",
    "word": "急行",
    "options": [
      "きゅうこう",
      "きかん",
      "さんぽする",
      "しゅうまつ"
    ],
    "correct": "きゅうこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"普通\"?",
    "word": "普通",
    "options": [
      "しあい",
      "つき",
      "こくさい",
      "ふつう"
    ],
    "correct": "ふつう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"特別\"?",
    "word": "特別",
    "options": [
      "かのう",
      "しま",
      "とくべつ",
      "かいわ"
    ],
    "correct": "とくべつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"案内\"?",
    "word": "案内",
    "options": [
      "にがて",
      "ただしい",
      "ひく",
      "あんない"
    ],
    "correct": "あんない"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"予定\"?",
    "word": "予定",
    "options": [
      "ようじ",
      "おどろく",
      "とめる",
      "よてい"
    ],
    "correct": "よてい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"決定\"?",
    "word": "決定",
    "options": [
      "なおす",
      "せいじ",
      "けしき",
      "けってい"
    ],
    "correct": "けってい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"出席\"?",
    "word": "出席",
    "options": [
      "わかす",
      "ふむ",
      "かわく",
      "しゅっせき"
    ],
    "correct": "しゅっせき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"欠席\"?",
    "word": "欠席",
    "options": [
      "けっせき",
      "うたう",
      "ふべん",
      "やく"
    ],
    "correct": "けっせき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"座席\"?",
    "word": "座席",
    "options": [
      "ざせき",
      "おもい",
      "ねむい",
      "かたい"
    ],
    "correct": "ざせき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"海岸\"?",
    "word": "海岸",
    "options": [
      "ひつよう",
      "ちり",
      "かいがん",
      "ならぶ"
    ],
    "correct": "かいがん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"湖\"?",
    "word": "湖",
    "options": [
      "みずうみ",
      "ばんぐみ",
      "よてい",
      "しょくじ"
    ],
    "correct": "みずうみ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"島\"?",
    "word": "島",
    "options": [
      "さびしい",
      "せいぶつ",
      "かなしむ",
      "しま"
    ],
    "correct": "しま"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"港\"?",
    "word": "港",
    "options": [
      "あう",
      "わすれる",
      "みなと",
      "すわる"
    ],
    "correct": "みなと"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"村\"?",
    "word": "村",
    "options": [
      "むら",
      "おもいだす",
      "つうやく",
      "ちり"
    ],
    "correct": "むら"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"町\"?",
    "word": "町",
    "options": [
      "まち",
      "あつまる",
      "さんかする",
      "わかもの"
    ],
    "correct": "まち"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"都会\"?",
    "word": "都会",
    "options": [
      "おこる",
      "ひえる",
      "とかい",
      "へた"
    ],
    "correct": "とかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"田舎\"?",
    "word": "田舎",
    "options": [
      "いなか",
      "じしょ",
      "こしょう",
      "せんたくする"
    ],
    "correct": "いなか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"景色\"?",
    "word": "景色",
    "options": [
      "けしき",
      "せいじ",
      "しゃかい",
      "うんてんする"
    ],
    "correct": "けしき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"自然\"?",
    "word": "自然",
    "options": [
      "しぜん",
      "ほうりつ",
      "おこる",
      "とまる"
    ],
    "correct": "しぜん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"空気\"?",
    "word": "空気",
    "options": [
      "くうき",
      "しけん",
      "すばらしい",
      "ふゆ"
    ],
    "correct": "くうき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"地震\"?",
    "word": "地震",
    "options": [
      "ざっし",
      "じしん",
      "きぶん",
      "すわる"
    ],
    "correct": "じしん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"火事\"?",
    "word": "火事",
    "options": [
      "しぜん",
      "かじ",
      "しゅくだい",
      "しょくじする"
    ],
    "correct": "かじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"事故\"?",
    "word": "事故",
    "options": [
      "いみ",
      "ものがたり",
      "よしゅうする",
      "じこ"
    ],
    "correct": "じこ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"故障\"?",
    "word": "故障",
    "options": [
      "こしょう",
      "とまる",
      "かんけい",
      "そうだんする"
    ],
    "correct": "こしょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"台風\"?",
    "word": "台風",
    "options": [
      "たいふう",
      "せいかつ",
      "こわい",
      "いなか"
    ],
    "correct": "たいふう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"津波\"?",
    "word": "津波",
    "options": [
      "つなみ",
      "さいきん",
      "おくる",
      "おくれる"
    ],
    "correct": "つなみ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"洪水\"?",
    "word": "洪水",
    "options": [
      "しごと",
      "こうずい",
      "じかん",
      "おる"
    ],
    "correct": "こうずい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"太陽\"?",
    "word": "太陽",
    "options": [
      "まち",
      "かよう",
      "ほそい",
      "たいよう"
    ],
    "correct": "たいよう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"星\"?",
    "word": "星",
    "options": [
      "わかれる",
      "ほし",
      "ふむ",
      "たのしむ"
    ],
    "correct": "ほし"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"月\"?",
    "word": "月",
    "options": [
      "ちゅういする",
      "とくい",
      "どうぐ",
      "つき"
    ],
    "correct": "つき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"光\"?",
    "word": "光",
    "options": [
      "ひかり",
      "しゅみ",
      "こうじょう",
      "きょうみ"
    ],
    "correct": "ひかり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"季節\"?",
    "word": "季節",
    "options": [
      "じかん",
      "せんたくする",
      "すてる",
      "きせつ"
    ],
    "correct": "きせつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"春\"?",
    "word": "春",
    "options": [
      "こくさい",
      "かがく",
      "なおす",
      "はる"
    ],
    "correct": "はる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"夏\"?",
    "word": "夏",
    "options": [
      "はる",
      "なつ",
      "ねむる",
      "にっき"
    ],
    "correct": "なつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"秋\"?",
    "word": "秋",
    "options": [
      "あき",
      "こくさい",
      "しごと",
      "しんぶん"
    ],
    "correct": "あき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"冬\"?",
    "word": "冬",
    "options": [
      "ふゆ",
      "まいにち",
      "しらべる",
      "こしょう"
    ],
    "correct": "ふゆ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"動物\"?",
    "word": "動物",
    "options": [
      "どうぶつ",
      "ふえる",
      "すぎる",
      "ひく"
    ],
    "correct": "どうぶつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"植物\"?",
    "word": "植物",
    "options": [
      "ふくしゅうする",
      "にる",
      "しょくぶつ",
      "しあい"
    ],
    "correct": "しょくぶつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"生物\"?",
    "word": "生物",
    "options": [
      "せいぶつ",
      "ねむい",
      "べんり",
      "にがて"
    ],
    "correct": "せいぶつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"人間\"?",
    "word": "人間",
    "options": [
      "じしょ",
      "にんげん",
      "かなしむ",
      "しゅうまつ"
    ],
    "correct": "にんげん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"男性\"?",
    "word": "男性",
    "options": [
      "だんせい",
      "あさい",
      "せつめいする",
      "しあい"
    ],
    "correct": "だんせい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"女性\"?",
    "word": "女性",
    "options": [
      "かじ",
      "じょせい",
      "ちゅういする",
      "ふむ"
    ],
    "correct": "じょせい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"子供\"?",
    "word": "子供",
    "options": [
      "こしょう",
      "こども",
      "むら",
      "わすれる"
    ],
    "correct": "こども"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"若者\"?",
    "word": "若者",
    "options": [
      "まいにち",
      "わかもの",
      "あたためる",
      "きかい"
    ],
    "correct": "わかもの"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"老人\"?",
    "word": "老人",
    "options": [
      "あげる",
      "やく",
      "かたい",
      "ろうじん"
    ],
    "correct": "ろうじん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"将来\"?",
    "word": "将来",
    "options": [
      "しょうらい",
      "よしゅうする",
      "とおる",
      "どうぶつ"
    ],
    "correct": "しょうらい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"過去\"?",
    "word": "過去",
    "options": [
      "ひかる",
      "まいにち",
      "かこ",
      "にる"
    ],
    "correct": "かこ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"現在\"?",
    "word": "現在",
    "options": [
      "げんざい",
      "ざっし",
      "ふとる",
      "いみ"
    ],
    "correct": "げんざい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"時代\"?",
    "word": "時代",
    "options": [
      "じだい",
      "るすばん",
      "ふとる",
      "しょうたいする"
    ],
    "correct": "じだい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"毎日\"?",
    "word": "毎日",
    "options": [
      "まいにち",
      "かじ",
      "しゅくだい",
      "せんたくする"
    ],
    "correct": "まいにち"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"平日\"?",
    "word": "平日",
    "options": [
      "へいじつ",
      "わすれる",
      "しゃかい",
      "ざっし"
    ],
    "correct": "へいじつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"週末\"?",
    "word": "週末",
    "options": [
      "しゅうまつ",
      "おる",
      "おもいだす",
      "いわう"
    ],
    "correct": "しゅうまつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"月末\"?",
    "word": "月末",
    "options": [
      "げつまつ",
      "さんせいする",
      "すうがく",
      "こしょう"
    ],
    "correct": "げつまつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"年末\"?",
    "word": "年末",
    "options": [
      "とどく",
      "ねんまつ",
      "さいきん",
      "とくべつ"
    ],
    "correct": "ねんまつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"期間\"?",
    "word": "期間",
    "options": [
      "かんたん",
      "ひく",
      "あう",
      "きかん"
    ],
    "correct": "きかん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"時間\"?",
    "word": "時間",
    "options": [
      "ちり",
      "じかん",
      "ねむい",
      "しょうたいする"
    ],
    "correct": "じかん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"瞬間\"?",
    "word": "瞬間",
    "options": [
      "しゅんかん",
      "しけん",
      "しゃかい",
      "よしゅうする"
    ],
    "correct": "しゅんかん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"最近\"?",
    "word": "最近",
    "options": [
      "わる",
      "さいきん",
      "とどく",
      "なげる"
    ],
    "correct": "さいきん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"最初\"?",
    "word": "最初",
    "options": [
      "しぜん",
      "さいきん",
      "なつ",
      "さいしょ"
    ],
    "correct": "さいしょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"最後\"?",
    "word": "最後",
    "options": [
      "さいご",
      "しま",
      "おもいだす",
      "ぶんがく"
    ],
    "correct": "さいご"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"最近\"?",
    "word": "最近",
    "options": [
      "ふくしゅうする",
      "だいじ",
      "こわい",
      "さいきん"
    ],
    "correct": "さいきん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"日記\"?",
    "word": "日記",
    "options": [
      "あぶない",
      "のぼる",
      "はずかしい",
      "にっき"
    ],
    "correct": "にっき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"記事\"?",
    "word": "記事",
    "options": [
      "きじ",
      "ぎょうじ",
      "ざせき",
      "とくべつ"
    ],
    "correct": "きじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"新聞\"?",
    "word": "新聞",
    "options": [
      "おどろく",
      "みつける",
      "しんぶん",
      "とめる"
    ],
    "correct": "しんぶん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"雑誌\"?",
    "word": "雑誌",
    "options": [
      "ふえる",
      "おぼえる",
      "ざっし",
      "ふべん"
    ],
    "correct": "ざっし"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"広告\"?",
    "word": "広告",
    "options": [
      "こわい",
      "こうこく",
      "たのしむ",
      "しゃかい"
    ],
    "correct": "こうこく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"看板\"?",
    "word": "看板",
    "options": [
      "くもる",
      "つよい",
      "かんばん",
      "おどろく"
    ],
    "correct": "かんばん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"手紙\"?",
    "word": "手紙",
    "options": [
      "てがみ",
      "しごと",
      "きかん",
      "ばんぐみ"
    ],
    "correct": "てがみ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"書類\"?",
    "word": "書類",
    "options": [
      "しょるい",
      "すてる",
      "きかん",
      "じしん"
    ],
    "correct": "しょるい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"資料\"?",
    "word": "資料",
    "options": [
      "せいぶつ",
      "せんたくする",
      "あう",
      "しりょう"
    ],
    "correct": "しりょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"原稿\"?",
    "word": "原稿",
    "options": [
      "げんこう",
      "ばしょ",
      "しゅくだい",
      "けいさんする"
    ],
    "correct": "げんこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"翻訳\"?",
    "word": "翻訳",
    "options": [
      "ほんやく",
      "こども",
      "ちょうし",
      "とおる"
    ],
    "correct": "ほんやく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"通訳\"?",
    "word": "通訳",
    "options": [
      "つうやく",
      "かなしむ",
      "とまる",
      "あんしんする"
    ],
    "correct": "つうやく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"放送\"?",
    "word": "放送",
    "options": [
      "れきし",
      "ふくしゅうする",
      "けいさんする",
      "ほうそう"
    ],
    "correct": "ほうそう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"番組\"?",
    "word": "番組",
    "options": [
      "きびしい",
      "かがく",
      "とかい",
      "ばんぐみ"
    ],
    "correct": "ばんぐみ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"漫画\"?",
    "word": "漫画",
    "options": [
      "くもる",
      "ふとる",
      "かんたん",
      "まんが"
    ],
    "correct": "まんが"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"小説\"?",
    "word": "小説",
    "options": [
      "ふむ",
      "あんない",
      "かんばん",
      "しょうせつ"
    ],
    "correct": "しょうせつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"物語\"?",
    "word": "物語",
    "options": [
      "つなみ",
      "なく",
      "しけん",
      "ものがたり"
    ],
    "correct": "ものがたり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"会話\"?",
    "word": "会話",
    "options": [
      "しゃかい",
      "おどろく",
      "こうじょう",
      "かいわ"
    ],
    "correct": "かいわ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"電話\"?",
    "word": "電話",
    "options": [
      "ようじ",
      "でんわ",
      "ふべん",
      "あらう"
    ],
    "correct": "でんわ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"留守番\"?",
    "word": "留守番",
    "options": [
      "るすばん",
      "ねむい",
      "さんせいする",
      "ほし"
    ],
    "correct": "るすばん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"用事\"?",
    "word": "用事",
    "options": [
      "すぎる",
      "ようじ",
      "けしき",
      "かんじる"
    ],
    "correct": "ようじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"大事\"?",
    "word": "大事",
    "options": [
      "だいじ",
      "せいぶつ",
      "こしょう",
      "あさい"
    ],
    "correct": "だいじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"仕事\"?",
    "word": "仕事",
    "options": [
      "ひつよう",
      "しごと",
      "とおる",
      "ふくざつ"
    ],
    "correct": "しごと"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"家事\"?",
    "word": "家事",
    "options": [
      "かじ",
      "まち",
      "でんわ",
      "しょうせつ"
    ],
    "correct": "かじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"食事\"?",
    "word": "食事",
    "options": [
      "ふる",
      "せんたくする",
      "いためる",
      "しょくじ"
    ],
    "correct": "しょくじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"行事\"?",
    "word": "行事",
    "options": [
      "ふべん",
      "あらう",
      "ぎょうじ",
      "ひつよう"
    ],
    "correct": "ぎょうじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"返事\"?",
    "word": "返事",
    "options": [
      "へんじ",
      "ざせき",
      "きもち",
      "うごく"
    ],
    "correct": "へんじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"火事\"?",
    "word": "火事",
    "options": [
      "たのしむ",
      "すわる",
      "なく",
      "かじ"
    ],
    "correct": "かじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"用事\"?",
    "word": "用事",
    "options": [
      "ようじ",
      "しゃかい",
      "てつだう",
      "だんせい"
    ],
    "correct": "ようじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"安全\"?",
    "word": "安全",
    "options": [
      "あんぜん",
      "げんざい",
      "ものがたり",
      "なげる"
    ],
    "correct": "あんぜん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"危険\"?",
    "word": "危険",
    "options": [
      "じこ",
      "へる",
      "しゅうまつ",
      "きけん"
    ],
    "correct": "きけん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"必要\"?",
    "word": "必要",
    "options": [
      "げんこう",
      "げんざい",
      "かわる",
      "ひつよう"
    ],
    "correct": "ひつよう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"不便\"?",
    "word": "不便",
    "options": [
      "しょくじする",
      "かんたん",
      "ふべん",
      "みずうみ"
    ],
    "correct": "ふべん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"便利\"?",
    "word": "便利",
    "options": [
      "べんり",
      "よろこぶ",
      "れんらくする",
      "とかい"
    ],
    "correct": "べんり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"複雑\"?",
    "word": "複雑",
    "options": [
      "ふくざつ",
      "ひかり",
      "へいじつ",
      "おぼえる"
    ],
    "correct": "ふくざつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"簡単\"?",
    "word": "簡単",
    "options": [
      "かのう",
      "ひかり",
      "かんたん",
      "きめる"
    ],
    "correct": "かんたん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"無理\"?",
    "word": "無理",
    "options": [
      "かいわ",
      "むり",
      "ぶんがく",
      "はんたいする"
    ],
    "correct": "むり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"可能\"?",
    "word": "可能",
    "options": [
      "ふえる",
      "かのう",
      "つたえる",
      "かじ"
    ],
    "correct": "かのう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"有名\"?",
    "word": "有名",
    "options": [
      "ゆうめい",
      "にる",
      "やく",
      "よごす"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆうめい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"上手\"?",
    "word": "上手",
    "options": [
      "よやくする",
      "じょうず",
      "せつめいする",
      "かがく"
    ],
    "correct": "じょうず"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"下手\"?",
    "word": "下手",
    "options": [
      "へた",
      "ほんやく",
      "つき",
      "みなと"
    ],
    "correct": "へた"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"苦手\"?",
    "word": "苦手",
    "options": [
      "ぎょうじ",
      "まんが",
      "にがて",
      "じこ"
    ],
    "correct": "にがて"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"得意\"?",
    "word": "得意",
    "options": [
      "さいご",
      "じだい",
      "とくい",
      "ひやす"
    ],
    "correct": "とくい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"急ぐ\"?",
    "word": "急ぐ",
    "options": [
      "いそぐ",
      "かんがえる",
      "じかん",
      "しゃかい"
    ],
    "correct": "いそぐ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"遅れる\"?",
    "word": "遅れる",
    "options": [
      "おくれる",
      "こうじょう",
      "こしょう",
      "さんせいする"
    ],
    "correct": "おくれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"間に合う\"?",
    "word": "間に合う",
    "options": [
      "まにあう",
      "にる",
      "あげる",
      "おぼえる"
    ],
    "correct": "まにあう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"止まる\"?",
    "word": "止まる",
    "options": [
      "とまる",
      "ふく",
      "みずうみ",
      "かぐ"
    ],
    "correct": "とまる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"止める\"?",
    "word": "止める",
    "options": [
      "とめる",
      "しょうたいする",
      "うんてんする",
      "ゆうめい"
    ],
    "correct": "とめる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"動く\"?",
    "word": "動く",
    "options": [
      "とくべつ",
      "みずうみ",
      "ちり",
      "うごく"
    ],
    "correct": "うごく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"変える\"?",
    "word": "変える",
    "options": [
      "かえる",
      "みずうみ",
      "しま",
      "こうこく"
    ],
    "correct": "かえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"変わる\"?",
    "word": "変わる",
    "options": [
      "かわる",
      "れきし",
      "はる",
      "いためる"
    ],
    "correct": "かわる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"選ぶ\"?",
    "word": "選ぶ",
    "options": [
      "すぎる",
      "ぬすむ",
      "にっき",
      "えらぶ"
    ],
    "correct": "えらぶ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"決める\"?",
    "word": "決める",
    "options": [
      "ふくしゅうする",
      "あんないする",
      "きめる",
      "こうこく"
    ],
    "correct": "きめる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"比べる\"?",
    "word": "比べる",
    "options": [
      "くらべる",
      "ふくしゅうする",
      "こくさい",
      "げんこう"
    ],
    "correct": "くらべる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"調べる\"?",
    "word": "調べる",
    "options": [
      "あんないする",
      "しらべる",
      "とかい",
      "けしき"
    ],
    "correct": "しらべる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"見つける\"?",
    "word": "見つける",
    "options": [
      "せつめいする",
      "みつける",
      "ふくしゅうする",
      "へいじつ"
    ],
    "correct": "みつける"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"見つかる\"?",
    "word": "見つかる",
    "options": [
      "みつかる",
      "やく",
      "せかい",
      "ふくしゅうする"
    ],
    "correct": "みつかる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"届ける\"?",
    "word": "届ける",
    "options": [
      "あたためる",
      "とどける",
      "りょうりする",
      "いためる"
    ],
    "correct": "とどける"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"届く\"?",
    "word": "届く",
    "options": [
      "とどく",
      "じしん",
      "かんけい",
      "へいじつ"
    ],
    "correct": "とどく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"送る\"?",
    "word": "送る",
    "options": [
      "わかす",
      "うつくしい",
      "おくる",
      "おどる"
    ],
    "correct": "おくる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"払う\"?",
    "word": "払う",
    "options": [
      "しゅくだい",
      "ふとい",
      "はらう",
      "とくい"
    ],
    "correct": "はらう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"笑う\"?",
    "word": "笑う",
    "options": [
      "さんせいする",
      "ろうじん",
      "じかん",
      "わらう"
    ],
    "correct": "わらう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"泣く\"?",
    "word": "泣く",
    "options": [
      "ちり",
      "なく",
      "みずうみ",
      "きもち"
    ],
    "correct": "なく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"怒る\"?",
    "word": "怒る",
    "options": [
      "かわく",
      "うんどう",
      "ふる",
      "おこる"
    ],
    "correct": "おこる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"驚く\"?",
    "word": "驚く",
    "options": [
      "おどろく",
      "じこ",
      "ねむる",
      "みずうみ"
    ],
    "correct": "おどろく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"喜ぶ\"?",
    "word": "喜ぶ",
    "options": [
      "よろこぶ",
      "わる",
      "ひえる",
      "じかん"
    ],
    "correct": "よろこぶ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"悲しむ\"?",
    "word": "悲しむ",
    "options": [
      "かなしむ",
      "きゅうこう",
      "よごす",
      "いみ"
    ],
    "correct": "かなしむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"楽しむ\"?",
    "word": "楽しむ",
    "options": [
      "ひつよう",
      "たすける",
      "よごす",
      "たのしむ"
    ],
    "correct": "たのしむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"苦しむ\"?",
    "word": "苦しむ",
    "options": [
      "きけん",
      "ねがう",
      "くるしむ",
      "わらう"
    ],
    "correct": "くるしむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"悩む\"?",
    "word": "悩む",
    "options": [
      "なやむ",
      "ぎょうじ",
      "ぬすむ",
      "あつまる"
    ],
    "correct": "なやむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"望む\"?",
    "word": "望む",
    "options": [
      "ぶんがく",
      "のぞむ",
      "ふゆ",
      "かのう"
    ],
    "correct": "のぞむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"願う\"?",
    "word": "願う",
    "options": [
      "ひかり",
      "やせる",
      "ねがう",
      "きかん"
    ],
    "correct": "ねがう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"信じる\"?",
    "word": "信じる",
    "options": [
      "みずうみ",
      "あつまる",
      "かこ",
      "しんじる"
    ],
    "correct": "しんじる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"疑う\"?",
    "word": "疑う",
    "options": [
      "しま",
      "うたがう",
      "はずかしい",
      "さいご"
    ],
    "correct": "うたがう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"感じる\"?",
    "word": "感じる",
    "options": [
      "かんじる",
      "ひく",
      "ひやす",
      "おどる"
    ],
    "correct": "かんじる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"考える\"?",
    "word": "考える",
    "options": [
      "かんがえる",
      "すわる",
      "はんたいする",
      "いためる"
    ],
    "correct": "かんがえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"覚える\"?",
    "word": "覚える",
    "options": [
      "おぼえる",
      "へた",
      "いなか",
      "りょうりする"
    ],
    "correct": "おぼえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"忘れる\"?",
    "word": "忘れる",
    "options": [
      "そうじする",
      "わすれる",
      "かいがん",
      "みずうみ"
    ],
    "correct": "わすれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"思い出す\"?",
    "word": "思い出す",
    "options": [
      "ちがう",
      "ゆうめい",
      "ようじ",
      "おもいだす"
    ],
    "correct": "おもいだす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"伝える\"?",
    "word": "伝える",
    "options": [
      "つたえる",
      "でんわ",
      "りゆう",
      "しゃかい"
    ],
    "correct": "つたえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"教える\"?",
    "word": "教える",
    "options": [
      "しけん",
      "おしえる",
      "ぶんか",
      "ざせき"
    ],
    "correct": "おしえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"習う\"?",
    "word": "習う",
    "options": [
      "きもち",
      "ならう",
      "よしゅうする",
      "くらべる"
    ],
    "correct": "ならう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"通う\"?",
    "word": "通う",
    "options": [
      "かよう",
      "しんぱいする",
      "しけん",
      "しゃかい"
    ],
    "correct": "かよう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"辞める\"?",
    "word": "辞める",
    "options": [
      "さいしょ",
      "めずらしい",
      "やめる",
      "つなみ"
    ],
    "correct": "やめる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"集まる\"?",
    "word": "集まる",
    "options": [
      "こうじょう",
      "さんかする",
      "こくさい",
      "あつまる"
    ],
    "correct": "あつまる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"集める\"?",
    "word": "集める",
    "options": [
      "あつめる",
      "しゃかい",
      "まち",
      "うつ"
    ],
    "correct": "あつめる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"別れる\"?",
    "word": "別れる",
    "options": [
      "はらう",
      "わかれる",
      "おしえる",
      "ようじ"
    ],
    "correct": "わかれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"違う\"?",
    "word": "違う",
    "options": [
      "なく",
      "わたる",
      "ちがう",
      "わすれる"
    ],
    "correct": "ちがう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"似る\"?",
    "word": "似る",
    "options": [
      "しらべる",
      "げんこう",
      "せいかつ",
      "にる"
    ],
    "correct": "にる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"合う\"?",
    "word": "合う",
    "options": [
      "あう",
      "ふとい",
      "さんせいする",
      "りょうりする"
    ],
    "correct": "あう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"間に合う\"?",
    "word": "間に合う",
    "options": [
      "なく",
      "かじ",
      "とどく",
      "まにあう"
    ],
    "correct": "まにあう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"手伝う\"?",
    "word": "手伝う",
    "options": [
      "かんけい",
      "てつだう",
      "みつかる",
      "どうぐ"
    ],
    "correct": "てつだう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"助ける\"?",
    "word": "助ける",
    "options": [
      "たすける",
      "こしょう",
      "しんぶん",
      "いわう"
    ],
    "correct": "たすける"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"祈る\"?",
    "word": "祈る",
    "options": [
      "あつめる",
      "くらべる",
      "とまる",
      "いのる"
    ],
    "correct": "いのる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"祝う\"?",
    "word": "祝う",
    "options": [
      "ねんまつ",
      "いわう",
      "ようじ",
      "けいざい"
    ],
    "correct": "いわう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"慣れる\"?",
    "word": "慣れる",
    "options": [
      "みずうみ",
      "こくさい",
      "なれる",
      "わる"
    ],
    "correct": "なれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"晴れる\"?",
    "word": "晴れる",
    "options": [
      "しあい",
      "はれる",
      "てつだう",
      "はんたいする"
    ],
    "correct": "はれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"曇る\"?",
    "word": "曇る",
    "options": [
      "くもる",
      "なげる",
      "すうがく",
      "ばんぐみ"
    ],
    "correct": "くもる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"光る\"?",
    "word": "光る",
    "options": [
      "ひかる",
      "ねむる",
      "さいきん",
      "やくそくする"
    ],
    "correct": "ひかる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"吹く\"?",
    "word": "吹く",
    "options": [
      "にっき",
      "のぼる",
      "こうじょう",
      "ふく"
    ],
    "correct": "ふく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"降る\"?",
    "word": "降る",
    "options": [
      "ひやす",
      "ふる",
      "やくそくする",
      "さいご"
    ],
    "correct": "ふる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"冷える\"?",
    "word": "冷える",
    "options": [
      "ひえる",
      "わる",
      "しけん",
      "やくそくする"
    ],
    "correct": "ひえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"冷やす\"?",
    "word": "冷やす",
    "options": [
      "じしん",
      "さんぽする",
      "ひやす",
      "まち"
    ],
    "correct": "ひやす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"温める\"?",
    "word": "温める",
    "options": [
      "なれる",
      "あたためる",
      "やわらかい",
      "ひつよう"
    ],
    "correct": "あたためる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"沸かす\"?",
    "word": "沸かす",
    "options": [
      "さいしょ",
      "うつ",
      "ひかり",
      "わかす"
    ],
    "correct": "わかす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"焼く\"?",
    "word": "焼く",
    "options": [
      "しゅうまつ",
      "ふつう",
      "うごく",
      "やく"
    ],
    "correct": "やく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"煮る\"?",
    "word": "煮る",
    "options": [
      "しゅんかん",
      "かいわ",
      "にる",
      "おもい"
    ],
    "correct": "にる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"揚げる\"?",
    "word": "揚げる",
    "options": [
      "じこ",
      "しんぶん",
      "あげる",
      "ぎじゅつ"
    ],
    "correct": "あげる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"炒める\"?",
    "word": "炒める",
    "options": [
      "いためる",
      "きけん",
      "しけん",
      "とかい"
    ],
    "correct": "いためる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"包む\"?",
    "word": "包む",
    "options": [
      "ぶんか",
      "まんが",
      "つつむ",
      "やわらかい"
    ],
    "correct": "つつむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"運ぶ\"?",
    "word": "運ぶ",
    "options": [
      "ひつよう",
      "かわる",
      "にる",
      "はこぶ"
    ],
    "correct": "はこぶ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"投げる\"?",
    "word": "投げる",
    "options": [
      "けしき",
      "ものがたり",
      "なげる",
      "たいふう"
    ],
    "correct": "なげる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"打つ\"?",
    "word": "打つ",
    "options": [
      "ふむ",
      "なおす",
      "ひえる",
      "うつ"
    ],
    "correct": "うつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"押す\"?",
    "word": "押す",
    "options": [
      "たいふう",
      "あう",
      "おす",
      "ほんやく"
    ],
    "correct": "おす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"引く\"?",
    "word": "引く",
    "options": [
      "ひく",
      "じだい",
      "へる",
      "しあい"
    ],
    "correct": "ひく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"折る\"?",
    "word": "折る",
    "options": [
      "おる",
      "にっき",
      "よしゅうする",
      "なおす"
    ],
    "correct": "おる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"割る\"?",
    "word": "割る",
    "options": [
      "しま",
      "わる",
      "みずうみ",
      "あつめる"
    ],
    "correct": "わる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"切る\"?",
    "word": "切る",
    "options": [
      "まち",
      "ぎょうじ",
      "ちり",
      "きる"
    ],
    "correct": "きる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"貼る\"?",
    "word": "貼る",
    "options": [
      "はる",
      "ふつう",
      "とくい",
      "あんしんする"
    ],
    "correct": "はる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"振る\"?",
    "word": "振る",
    "options": [
      "いなか",
      "ふる",
      "ひく",
      "しゃかい"
    ],
    "correct": "ふる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"踏む\"?",
    "word": "踏む",
    "options": [
      "ふむ",
      "きけん",
      "れんしゅうする",
      "ふつう"
    ],
    "correct": "ふむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"踊る\"?",
    "word": "踊る",
    "options": [
      "はる",
      "おどる",
      "わかす",
      "やめる"
    ],
    "correct": "おどる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"歌う\"?",
    "word": "歌う",
    "options": [
      "おこる",
      "うたう",
      "あんしんする",
      "けんぶつする"
    ],
    "correct": "うたう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"描く\"?",
    "word": "描く",
    "options": [
      "ひえる",
      "こしょう",
      "かく",
      "てつだう"
    ],
    "correct": "かく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"並べる\"?",
    "word": "並べる",
    "options": [
      "しんぱいする",
      "すうがく",
      "ならべる",
      "よろこぶ"
    ],
    "correct": "ならべる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"並ぶ\"?",
    "word": "並ぶ",
    "options": [
      "さんせいする",
      "かのう",
      "ならぶ",
      "れんしゅうする"
    ],
    "correct": "ならぶ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"座る\"?",
    "word": "座る",
    "options": [
      "へた",
      "すわる",
      "ほうりつ",
      "ふべん"
    ],
    "correct": "すわる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"眠る\"?",
    "word": "眠る",
    "options": [
      "ばんぐみ",
      "かなしむ",
      "ねむる",
      "まにあう"
    ],
    "correct": "ねむる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"訪ねる\"?",
    "word": "訪ねる",
    "options": [
      "りゆう",
      "あんしんする",
      "たずねる",
      "すてる"
    ],
    "correct": "たずねる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"尋ねる\"?",
    "word": "尋ねる",
    "options": [
      "ほんやく",
      "きじ",
      "わかす",
      "たずねる"
    ],
    "correct": "たずねる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"泊まる\"?",
    "word": "泊まる",
    "options": [
      "とまる",
      "あき",
      "めずらしい",
      "けいざい"
    ],
    "correct": "とまる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"通る\"?",
    "word": "通る",
    "options": [
      "ねんまつ",
      "いためる",
      "いなか",
      "とおる"
    ],
    "correct": "とおる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"渡る\"?",
    "word": "渡る",
    "options": [
      "わたる",
      "じょせい",
      "へた",
      "やめる"
    ],
    "correct": "わたる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"登る\"?",
    "word": "登る",
    "options": [
      "きびしい",
      "すてる",
      "はなれる",
      "のぼる"
    ],
    "correct": "のぼる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"下りる\"?",
    "word": "下りる",
    "options": [
      "しょるい",
      "かえる",
      "おりる",
      "だいじ"
    ],
    "correct": "おりる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"向かう\"?",
    "word": "向かう",
    "options": [
      "しゅんかん",
      "せつめいする",
      "むかう",
      "ふとい"
    ],
    "correct": "むかう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"過ぎる\"?",
    "word": "過ぎる",
    "options": [
      "すぎる",
      "ほし",
      "じゆう",
      "そうだんする"
    ],
    "correct": "すぎる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"離れる\"?",
    "word": "離れる",
    "options": [
      "きけん",
      "けしき",
      "うつくしい",
      "はなれる"
    ],
    "correct": "はなれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"急ぐ\"?",
    "word": "急ぐ",
    "options": [
      "いそぐ",
      "ひどい",
      "せいぶつ",
      "さいきん"
    ],
    "correct": "いそぐ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"拾う\"?",
    "word": "拾う",
    "options": [
      "ちゅういする",
      "しゃかい",
      "しゅくだい",
      "ひろう"
    ],
    "correct": "ひろう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"捨てる\"?",
    "word": "捨てる",
    "options": [
      "すてる",
      "しゅうまつ",
      "けんぶつする",
      "こうずい"
    ],
    "correct": "すてる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"盗む\"?",
    "word": "盗む",
    "options": [
      "ぬすむ",
      "とくい",
      "じだい",
      "れんしゅうする"
    ],
    "correct": "ぬすむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"壊す\"?",
    "word": "壊す",
    "options": [
      "こわす",
      "おもい",
      "へいじつ",
      "せいかつ"
    ],
    "correct": "こわす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"治す\"?",
    "word": "治す",
    "options": [
      "はんたいする",
      "なおす",
      "おくれる",
      "しゃかい"
    ],
    "correct": "なおす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"直す\"?",
    "word": "直す",
    "options": [
      "しゅくだい",
      "なおす",
      "こども",
      "はる"
    ],
    "correct": "なおす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"汚す\"?",
    "word": "汚す",
    "options": [
      "おす",
      "ふとい",
      "よごす",
      "みつける"
    ],
    "correct": "よごす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"洗う\"?",
    "word": "洗う",
    "options": [
      "あらう",
      "しま",
      "へる",
      "わらう"
    ],
    "correct": "あらう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"乾く\"?",
    "word": "乾く",
    "options": [
      "そうじする",
      "いみ",
      "きゅうこう",
      "かわく"
    ],
    "correct": "かわく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"濡れる\"?",
    "word": "濡れる",
    "options": [
      "しょくじする",
      "しょうせつ",
      "ぬれる",
      "ひつよう"
    ],
    "correct": "ぬれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"太る\"?",
    "word": "太る",
    "options": [
      "ねむる",
      "うつくしい",
      "にる",
      "ふとる"
    ],
    "correct": "ふとる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"痩せる\"?",
    "word": "痩せる",
    "options": [
      "しょくじ",
      "はこぶ",
      "やせる",
      "へいじつ"
    ],
    "correct": "やせる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"増える\"?",
    "word": "増える",
    "options": [
      "けいざい",
      "しんぱいする",
      "かいがん",
      "ふえる"
    ],
    "correct": "ふえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"減る\"?",
    "word": "減る",
    "options": [
      "やめる",
      "はる",
      "へる",
      "かえる"
    ],
    "correct": "へる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"重い\"?",
    "word": "重い",
    "options": [
      "おもい",
      "かく",
      "とどける",
      "ならう"
    ],
    "correct": "おもい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"軽い\"?",
    "word": "軽い",
    "options": [
      "ふとい",
      "こわい",
      "かいわ",
      "かるい"
    ],
    "correct": "かるい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"太い\"?",
    "word": "太い",
    "options": [
      "ばしょ",
      "かがく",
      "はる",
      "ふとい"
    ],
    "correct": "ふとい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"細い\"?",
    "word": "細い",
    "options": [
      "ほそい",
      "ふゆ",
      "ようじ",
      "あき"
    ],
    "correct": "ほそい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"固い\"?",
    "word": "固い",
    "options": [
      "かたい",
      "ろうじん",
      "おどる",
      "あらう"
    ],
    "correct": "かたい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"柔らかい\"?",
    "word": "柔らかい",
    "options": [
      "かよう",
      "つたえる",
      "じょうず",
      "やわらかい"
    ],
    "correct": "やわらかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"強い\"?",
    "word": "強い",
    "options": [
      "つよい",
      "はる",
      "みつかる",
      "ゆうめい"
    ],
    "correct": "つよい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"弱い\"?",
    "word": "弱い",
    "options": [
      "よわい",
      "えらぶ",
      "ふる",
      "しらべる"
    ],
    "correct": "よわい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"深い\"?",
    "word": "深い",
    "options": [
      "ふかい",
      "わかれる",
      "あんないする",
      "ちり"
    ],
    "correct": "ふかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"浅い\"?",
    "word": "浅い",
    "options": [
      "かいわ",
      "じだい",
      "やめる",
      "あさい"
    ],
    "correct": "あさい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"美しい\"?",
    "word": "美しい",
    "options": [
      "へいじつ",
      "うつくしい",
      "まいにち",
      "こくさい"
    ],
    "correct": "うつくしい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"珍しい\"?",
    "word": "珍しい",
    "options": [
      "なく",
      "つつむ",
      "じょうず",
      "めずらしい"
    ],
    "correct": "めずらしい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"素晴らしい\"?",
    "word": "素晴らしい",
    "options": [
      "すばらしい",
      "へんじ",
      "ぎょうじ",
      "ひえる"
    ],
    "correct": "すばらしい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"恥ずかしい\"?",
    "word": "恥ずかしい",
    "options": [
      "つうやく",
      "はずかしい",
      "かんじる",
      "ぐあい"
    ],
    "correct": "はずかしい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"厳しい\"?",
    "word": "厳しい",
    "options": [
      "かんがえる",
      "れんしゅうする",
      "きびしい",
      "ものがたり"
    ],
    "correct": "きびしい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"正しい\"?",
    "word": "正しい",
    "options": [
      "ただしい",
      "せいかつ",
      "こうずい",
      "いためる"
    ],
    "correct": "ただしい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"珍しい\"?",
    "word": "珍しい",
    "options": [
      "ひえる",
      "いわう",
      "あさい",
      "めずらしい"
    ],
    "correct": "めずらしい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"酷い\"?",
    "word": "酷い",
    "options": [
      "ものがたり",
      "れんしゅうする",
      "たのしむ",
      "ひどい"
    ],
    "correct": "ひどい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"怖い\"?",
    "word": "怖い",
    "options": [
      "しけん",
      "くうき",
      "ねむる",
      "こわい"
    ],
    "correct": "こわい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"危ない\"?",
    "word": "危ない",
    "options": [
      "ぬすむ",
      "たいよう",
      "あぶない",
      "めずらしい"
    ],
    "correct": "あぶない"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"寂しい\"?",
    "word": "寂しい",
    "options": [
      "さびしい",
      "くるしむ",
      "こわす",
      "ねむい"
    ],
    "correct": "さびしい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"苦しい\"?",
    "word": "苦しい",
    "options": [
      "じしん",
      "くるしい",
      "じだい",
      "ふつう"
    ],
    "correct": "くるしい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"眠い\"?",
    "word": "眠い",
    "options": [
      "ねむい",
      "はんたいする",
      "せいかつ",
      "さいきん"
    ],
    "correct": "ねむい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"汚い\"?",
    "word": "汚い",
    "options": [
      "きたない",
      "ふとい",
      "くうき",
      "へいじつ"
    ],
    "correct": "きたない"
  }
]